moneypakpromotion.com 2011-06-10

# Green Dot Privacy Policy

## MONEYPAK TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE

These terms and conditions are effective as of August 2009  
and replace any previous MoneyPak terms and conditions.

Privacy Policy of Green Dot Corporation (“Green Dot”)

Green Dot values your trust and respects your expectation of privacy. As such, we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal financial information. This document outlines our privacy policy in connection with the nonpublic personal information we receive regarding you.

Collection and Use of Information About You. We collect nonpublic personal information about you in order to understand your needs, administer our business, process your transactions, and provide you with products and services. We obtain nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

Information you provide to us by telephone, on applications, in membership requests, at our web site, and on other forms (such as your name, address, telephone number and date of birth);  
Information about your transactions with us, joint marketers, or others (such as your MoneyPak balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and MoneyPak usage); and  
Our Disclosure of Information. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as insurance agents, so that they can market goods and services to you. We also may disclose:

Some of this information, such as your name and address, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf (e.g., to companies that assist us with mailings).  
Information about your MoneyPak and transactions: (a) where it is necessary or helpful to effect, process or confirm your transactions; (b) to verify the existence and availability of funds associated with your MoneyPak; (c) to comply with legal process, such as subpoenas and court orders; (d) to law enforcement authorities if we believe a crime has been committed; and (e) if you give us your consent.  
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about our current or former customers to unaffiliated third parties except as set forth in this policy or as permitted by law.

Information Security. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to our employees who have a need to know such information (e.g., to process your transactions). We train our employees on the importance of customer privacy and confidentiality. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard the nonpublic personal information of our customers.

Other Privacy Rights. We will comply with applicable state laws regarding the information we share about you. Certain state laws restrict the types of information that we may disclose about you or require that we provide you with additional notices or opt-out rights. If our records reflect that you are a resident of Vermont, for example, our sharing of information about you with nonaffiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements will be limited to information about your name, contact information, and our own transactions and experiences with you.

Changes to this Policy. We may add to, delete from, or otherwise change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a notice of the change (or an amended Privacy Policy) at our website, [www.moneypak.com](http://www.moneypak.com/). If required by law, we will send you a notice of the change. Your continued use of any service following such notification will constitute evidence of your agreement to the revised Policy.

Questions. If you have any questions regarding this Policy, write to us at Green Dot Customer Service, P.O. Box 1187, Monrovia, California 91017.
